Never gonna give you up, never gonna let you down, never gonna run around and desert you
永遠不會放棄你 永遠不會讓你失望 永遠不會四處遊蕩拋下你
We will, we will rock you
我們會 我們會震撼你
Sing it!
唱吧！
Oh girls just wanna have fun
女孩只想玩得開心
Yeah, I wanna dance with somebody
我想和某人共舞
With somebody who loves me
和愛我的人
With somebody, somebody, somebody
和某人 某人 某人
Look man, you can't touch this
小子 你碰不到這節奏
You better get hype, boy
嗨起來吧 兄弟
Cause you know you can't, you can't touch this
因為你碰不到 碰不到這節奏
Jump!
跳！
Go ahead and jump
儘管跳吧
I'm a mama
我是個辣媽
My bigger, she taught her for some
她教她如何生存
My bigger, to handle their guns
她教她如何應對槍械
Oh, we're halfway there
我們已經走到一半
Oh, give me all my prayer
靠著祈禱而活
Alla tu cuero pa'legria, Macarena
把你的身體獻給歡樂 馬卡蓮娜
This is dinner
這是顫慄之夜
Dinner at night
驚魂之夜
And no one's gonna save them
沒有人會拯救他們
Everybody!
大家！
Rock your body!
搖擺你的身體！
In the midnight now, she's got no more hope
在午夜時分 她已不再抱有希望
We're the rebel, yeah
我們就是叛逆者
Gimme, gimme, gimme our man at midnight
給我 給我 給我午夜的男人
Somebody help me chase this channel away
誰來幫我驅散這感覺
Callin' Mr. Raider, callin' Mr. Brown, callin' Mr. Bane
呼叫雷德先生 布朗先生 班恩先生
I'm looking for some hot stuff, baby, this evening I need some hot stuff, baby, tonight
我在找點火熱的 今晚我需要火熱的
This one's for hire, even if we're just dancing in the dark
這一首獻給我 就算我們只在黑暗中起舞
What is love? Baby, don't hurt me, don't hurt me, no more
什麼是愛 寶貝別傷我 別再傷我
You, you make my dreams come true
你讓我的夢想成真
You're a brother away, you're a mother, you're stayin' alive, stayin' alive
無論你是兄弟還是母親 我們要活著 活著
We're the city breakin' and everybody shakin' and we're stayin' alive
城市在沸騰 每個人都在搖擺 我們要活著
They're comin' to wreck me, I'm a dead man, stupid
他們要來毀掉我 我是個死人了 笨蛋
I'm a dead man, I'm a dead man, I'm a dead man, I'm a dead man, I'm a dead man
我是個死人 死人 死人 死人 死人
Don't stop me now
現在別阻止我
I'm havin' such a good time, I'm havin' a ball
我玩得超開心 嗨到不行
Hip Hop Hooray! Ho! Hey! Ho! Hey!
嘻哈萬歲 嘿！嘿！嘿！嘿！
Celebration!
慶祝！
We go celebrate and have a good time
我們去慶祝 玩個痛快
You're the one that I want!
你就是我的唯一！
Yeah, I'm the one!
沒錯 就是我！
Boo! Boo! Boo!
嗚！嗚！嗚！
Honey, you're the one that I want!
甜心 你就是我的唯一！
Yeah, I'm the one!
沒錯 就是我！
Go! Go!
前進！前進！
Upside, inside out
上下顛倒 由內到外
She's livin' to be thine own kind
她活出自己
Wake me up, before you go
在你離開前叫醒我
Don't believe me, hangin' on like a yo-yo
別相信我 像溜溜球般擺盪
Ra-Ra-Rasputin, lover of the Russian queen
拉-拉-拉斯普丁 俄羅斯女皇的情人
There was a cat that really was gone
有一隻貓真的消失了
That's this
就是這樣
Put on your red shoes and dance the blues
穿上你的紅鞋 跳出藍調
I've got the power
我擁有力量
That's the way, uh-huh, I like it, uh-huh, that's the way, uh-huh, I like it
就是這樣 嗯哼 我喜歡 就是這樣 嗯哼 我喜歡
I'm your Venus, I'm your fire, your desire
我是你的維納斯 你的火焰 你的渴望
A little bit of Monica in my life, a little bit of Erica by my side
生命中有一點莫妮卡 身邊有一點艾瑞卡
You're my heart, you're my soul, I keep it shining everywhere I go
你是我的心 我的靈魂 無論走到哪都閃閃發亮
It's the final countdown!
最後倒數開始！
Come on, let's go!
走吧 出發！
Let your body move to the music!
讓你的身體隨音樂擺動！
You spin me right round, baby, right round
你讓我團團轉 寶貝 團團轉
Like a record, baby, right round, round, round
像唱片一樣 寶貝 轉啊轉
She's a maniac, maniac at showdown
她是個瘋子 對決中的狂人
My girl wants to party all the time, party all the time, party all the time
我的女孩只想整夜狂歡 整夜狂歡 整夜狂歡
Ya ya ya, Coco Jumbo, ya ya ya
呀呀呀 可可俊博 呀呀呀
Ya ya ya, Coco Jumbo
呀呀呀 可可俊博
Something strange in the neighborhood
鄰里間有怪事發生
Who you gonna call?
你要打給誰？
Ghostbusters!
魔鬼剋星！
She's fresh, fresh, exciting
她清新 清新 令人興奮
She's so exciting to me, yeah
她讓我無比興奮
Everybody back now!
大家退後！
Shot to the heart in your two days
兩天之內射中心臟
You gave us a brand new day
你給了我們嶄新的一天
I've had the time of my life
我度過了人生最美好的時光
Never felt this way before
從未有過這種感覺
Ain't nobody so right
沒有人如此完美
Nothing better than
再也沒有比這更好的
Make me happy
讓我快樂
Here comes the outstripe, I'm the lyrical gangsta, excuse me Mr. Officer
我來了 饒舌悍匪 不好意思 警察先生
I love rock'n'roll, sweet love, I'm in the chipmunk, baby, I love rock'n'roll
我愛搖滾 甜蜜的愛 我愛搖滾 寶貝
When I'm in the dancing, it's a source of anger, you can feel it everywhere
當我起舞時 那是力量的源頭 你到處都感受得到
Don't blame it on sunshine, don't blame it on moonlight, don't blame it on good times, blame it on a boogie
別怪陽光 別怪月光 別怪美好時光 怪那布吉舞
I'm a bobby girl, in the bobby world, at these last weeks, I'm dancing
我是芭比女孩 在芭比世界裡 整夜都在跳舞
Oh, you to me are everything, the sweetest song that I could sing, oh baby
你是我的一切 我能唱出最甜的歌 寶貝
When farmer, you know say that I'm a snowman, I've got land, I like it boom boom down
你說我是冰雪人 砰砰砰 倒下
Take that money, I say say that I'm a snowman, say
拿著那錢 我說我是冰雪人 說吧
Oh no not I, I will survive, oh as long as I know how to survive, I know I'll still lie
不 我不會倒下 我會活下去 只要知道怎麼活 我會撐下去
I'm blue, I'm a beat, I'm a light
我憂鬱 我是個節拍 我是道光
I like to move it, move it
我喜歡動次動次
Yes we were born, given duty for him
我們為他而生 為他而戰
Born to be alive, born to be alive
生來就該活著 生來就該活著
P-push it real good
用力推
You are the dancing queen, young and sweet, only seventeen
你是跳舞皇后 年輕甜美 只有十七歲
Oh yeah, back in the summer of 69
沒錯 回到六九年那個夏天
I got five on it, it's got me stuck and I'm so bad
我押了五塊 我被它困住 太爽了
I got five on it
我押了五塊
Vamos a la playa, oh, oh, oh Vamos a la playa, oh, oh, oh
我們去海邊 喔喔喔 我們去海邊 喔喔喔
Open up my eyes for the sign Open up my eyes for the sign
為那道光開啟我的眼睛
Don't stop believing Hold on to that feeling
別放棄希望 守住那份感覺
Everybody's taking the chance And save the dance
每個人都在抓住機會 拯救這舞蹈
And I've been scatting at you. I've been very long time ago. Where did you come from? Where did you go? Where did you come from? Scatting at you.
我一直在嘶吼 那是好久以前 你從哪來 你到哪去 你從哪來 對你嘶吼
Do you believe in life after love?
你相信愛過之後還有愛嗎？
Change in love. Change in love.
愛的轉變 愛的轉變
I was made for loving you, baby. You were made for loving me.
我是為愛你而生 寶貝 你也是為愛我而生
Ice, ice, weenie, ice, ice, weenie
冰冰 小冰冰 冰冰 小冰冰
I just want your hands to return in your kiss
我只想要你的手 回到我的吻
Give me a sign, hit me baby one more time
給我一個訊號 寶貝再來一次
All right, all my boy, I'm ready, ready, ready
好啦 我準備好了 準備好了
Raise your little thing all over the floor
在地板上盡情搖擺
Para bailar la bamba se necesita con una poca de gracia
要跳巴姆巴舞 需要一點優雅
I'm kinda buzzed and it's all because this is how we do it
我有點嗨 因為我們就是這樣嗨的
South Central doesn't like nobody's a
中南區不甩任何人
Oh, too young, she's my oh, too young
她太年輕了 我的甜心 太年輕
Oh, hey, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
嘿 喔喔喔喔喔喔喔
I'm too sexy for my car, too sexy for my car, too sexy by far
我太性感了連車都配不上 遠遠超過
Take on me
擁抱我
You should be all night long
你應該整夜這樣
It's fun to stay at the YMCA
待在YMCA真有趣
It's fun to stay in the fire, in the CNA
待在這裡真有趣
How will I know if he really loves me?
我要怎麼知道他是否真的愛我
I say a prayer with every heartbeat
每次心跳我都祈禱
But the biggest kick I ever got
但我得到最大的快感
Was done a thing called the crocodile rock
就是跳那鱷魚搖滾
It's raining man!
天上掉男人啦！
Hallelujah, it's raining man!
哈利路亞 天上掉男人啦！
I feel love, I feel love, I feel love, I feel love, I feel love
我感受到愛 愛 愛 愛 愛
Video killed the radio star, video killed the radio star
影像殺了電台明星
I'm so excited and I just can't hide it, no, no, no, no, no
我超興奮藏不住 不不不不不
Whoop that ass, whoop that ass, whoop that ass
搖那屁股 搖那屁股 搖那屁股
If I'm in line out, I can feel your power, just like a bell
如果我站出來 我能感受你的力量 像鐘聲一樣
It's such a god-fuck-pressure
這真是太棒了
It's such a sweet decision
這是個甜蜜的決定
Now I gotta cut loose, put loose
現在我要解放 徹底放開
Kick off my leather shoes
踢掉我的皮鞋
I can't go down, but I can't forget
我無法倒下 也無法忘記
Take out the door to keep me down, I can't go down
把我擋在門外 我無法倒下
M-m-m-my Sharonda
我的莎朗達
So tonight I'm gonna party like it's 1999
今晚我要狂歡 像1999年那樣
Oh w-wow
哇
He's the greatest dancer
他是最棒的舞者
Oh w-wow
哇
That I've ever seen
是我見過最厲害的
Vital years happen to me
那些年發生在我身上
Right in front of my face
就在我眼前
my feelings can't describe it
難以形容我的感受
What I feel
我的感覺
Love Shack is a little old place where we can get together.
愛的小屋 是我們能相聚的老地方